These are my cross-eyed boots from Fernando Berlin and of course you can
wear them with a bodysuit but I'm going to show you an alternative today a catsuit
That's a catsuit, didn't try it on yet so we'll see
Oh my god, this is so much.
I'll put it inside.
I hate small zippers.
I kind of like the white stitching and there are thumb holes.
I'm normally wearing socks in my boots and heels and shoes.
This is just a try on video.
Chillax guys.
Oh my god, I tried.
Tada!
Like we had a look at myself.
I kind of like the jumpsuit and the corset part here in the top area.
Also the material mixed with the white stitching.
I think the boots look great with it.
But you know what comes next?
A belt.
And which belt?
My trusty trusty Norway design belt.
Because it looks good on everything.
Or maybe it's a bit too much this time.
Not sure.
Maybe I need a smaller belt, but you know, this still looks good.
How do you like it?
Do you have other ideas to combine these boots?
Let me know, but for now, this is my look.